A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 88), 1968-1990; bulk; 1.14; 12 Cubic Feet; 10 standard record storage boxes - Box R2401-R2408, R2410, R2411.
  - Program and Policy - Humanities, 911
    - Program and Policy - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Brumberg, Joan J., 1984-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Campbell, Mary S., 1984-1987 (Box R2410)
      - Cooper, Frederick, 1984-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Fuchs, Elinor, 1984-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Gillam, Richard, 1983-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Greenberg, Dolores, 1984 1986 (Box R2410)
      - Higonnet, Margaret R., 1984-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Higonnet, Patrice L.R., 1984-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Horowitz, Helen L., 1982-1985 1987 (Box R2410)
      - Hoxie, Frederick E., 1983-1984 1986-1987 (Box R2410)
      - Huggins, Nathan I., 1982-1984 1986-1987 (Box R2410)
      - Hylton, Peter W., 1983-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Jay, Martin-E., 1983-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Lears, T.J. Jackson, 1983-1984 1986-1987 (Box R2410)
      - Monas, Sidney, 1983-1985 1987 (Box R2410)
      - Moodie, Thomas D., 1983-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Perl, Jeffrey M., 1983-1984 1986 (Box R2410)
      - Rischin, Moses, 1982-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Rose, Phyllis, 1983-1986 (Box R2410)
      - Tinker, Catherine, 1979-1981 1983 (Box R2410)
      - Westfall, Richard S., 1983-1986 (Box R2410)
  - Program and Policy - Geographic Medicine, 928
    - Biomedical Research Center - Tropical medicine, 1977-1987 (Box R2411)
    - New England Medical Center - Immunoadjuvant, 1983-1984 1986 (Box R2411)
    - Program and Policy - Geographic Medicine - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Kazura, James Walter, 1978-1985 1987 (Box R2411)
      - Murray, Henry Wilke, 1980-1987 (Box R2411)
      - Schmidt-Ullrich, Rupert K.A., 1979-1987 (Box R2411)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 89), 1973-1991; bulk; 1.15; 44.4 Cubic Feet; Standard record storage boxes - Box R2412-Box R2448.
  Arranged primarily by Program, with a small volume of records arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1989.
  - United States, 200
    - Employment Program for Minority Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.), 1983-1987 (Box R2412)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) & suppl. files, 1982 (Box R2413)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Box R2414)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Box R2415)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Box R2416)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Box R2417)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Box R2418)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Box R2419)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Notebooks) (Box R2420)
    - EPMGFSP - Evaluation - (Abt Associates, Inc.) suppl. files (Notebooks) (Box R2421)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - AH 8505 National Humanities Center - American history teachers, 1983-1986 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8506 George Washington University - Humanities & public policy, 1985-1987 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8509 Painted Bride Art Center - Beck troupe, 1984-1987 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8513 Children's Museum (Boston) - Cross cultural programming, 1983-1987 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8515 Exploratorium - Artists-in-residence, 1982-1986 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8516 University of Maryland - Shakespeare Teachers Institute, 1984-1987 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8518 Newberry Library - Humanities conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8520 American Public Radio - Contemporary music, 1983-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8523 Arts International, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8525 PEN American Center - International congress, 1985-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8529 Symphony Space - Radio broadcast of lit. prog., 1984-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8530 New England Assn. of Schools & Colleges - Conference & suppl., 1982-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8533 Long Bow Group - China film, 1984-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8536 55th St. Dance Theatre Fd. - International touring, 1985-1986 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8539 Children's books feasibility study & suppl., 1985-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8518 Newberry Library - Humanities conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2422)
    - AH 8520 American Public Radio - Contemporary music, 1983-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8523 Arts International, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8525 PEN American Center - International congress, 1985-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8529 Symphony Space - Radio broadcast of lit. prog., 1984-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8530 New England Assn. of Schools & Colleges - Conference & Suppl., 1982-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8533 Long Bow Group - China film, 1984-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8536 55th St. Dance Theatre Fd.- International touring, 1985-1986 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8539 Children's books feasibility study & suppl., 1985-1987 (Box R2423)
    - AH 8540 Five Colleges, Inc - Humanities network, 1985-1987 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8549 American Council of Learned Societies - Visiting scholar data base, 1984-1987 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8602 Repertory Dance Theatre - 20th anniversary performances, 1985-198[?] (Box R2424)
    - AH 8603 Group I Acting Co. - "Orchards", 1985-1987 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8605 New York City Opera - Fire emergency fund for sets & costumes, 1985-1987 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8611 Readers International - Contemporary non-West. Lit, 1984-1987 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8617 Downtown Community Center - Building, 1986-1990 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8618 Center for Understanding Media - Picture opera, 1986-1987 (Box R2424)
    - AH 8631 Council of Chief State School Officers-Civil respon. con, 1986-1988 [unreadable] (Box R2424)
    - AH 8637 Minnesota Composers Forum - American music, 1986-1988 (Box R2425)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - AS 8506 University of Georgia - Wildlife manag. in Suriname, 1984-1985 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8508 International Society for Plant Molecular Biology - International congress, 1983-1986 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8509 International Lab. for Research on Animal Diseases-Jahnke, 1984-1985 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8512 International Fertilizer Development Center - Denitrification losses, 1984-1986 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8514 International Maize & Wheat Improve. Center-Wheat wide cross pr[unreadable], 1984-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8518 International Trypanotolerant Centre - Consultant, 1984-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8519 International Service for Nat. Agric. Res. - Consultants, 1985-1986 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8520 International Centre of Insect Physiology - Okeyo, 1985-1986 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8525 Philadelphia Society for Promoting Agric., 1984-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8526 International Rice Research Institute - Tissue culture lab. equip., 1985-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8529 ICLARM - Fund raising program, 1983-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8531 Fudan University - Institute of Genetics, 1985-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8533 Max Planck Institute for Plant Breeding - Electrotransformation, 1985-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8534 Winrock International Institute for Agric. Development - Conelly, 1985-1987 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8540 University of Florida - Gender issues in farming systems, 1985-1988 (Box R2425)
    - AS 8541 International Rice Research. Institute - Publication-Rice genetics, 1985-1988 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8542 Commonwealth Scientific Org. - Tissue culture, 1983-1987 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8601 University of California - Salt tolerance in cereals (Davis), 1984-1987 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8602 Biotech, of cereal crops - Workshop, 1985-1987 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8605 World Resources Institute - World Bank & International agr. development, 1985-1987 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8613 International Rice Research Institute - Sympos. - Chromosome eng. in plants, 1985-1987 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8617 International Center of Insect Physiology & Ecology-Review, 1986-198[?] (Box R2426)
    - AS 8623 IRRI - Workshop on biotech. for crop improvement, 1986-1988 (Box R2426)
    - AS 8631 ICLARM - Tilapia breeding, 1986-1987 (Box R2426)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - EO 8502 Baylor College of Medicine - Math & science impr. conf., 1984-1986 (Box R2426)
    - EO 8504 City College - Science graduate study, 1982-1987 (Box R2426)
    - EO 8509 Exploratorium - Explainer program, 1984-1987 (Box R2426)
    - EO 8510 Tulane University - Voting rights conf., 1984-1986 (Box R2427)
    - EO 8512 Inuit Circumpolar Conference - Alaska native claims., 1984-1987 (Box R2427)
    - EO 8514 Mississippi Action for Community Education - Citizen empowerment, 1984-1987 (Box R2427)
    - EO 8515 University of Michigan - Black election study (sppl. files in next box), 1983-1985 1988-1989 (Box R2427)
    - EO 8515 University of Michigan - Black election study suppl files (Box R2428)
    - EO 8518 Lewin, Ellen, 1985-1989 (Box R2428)
    - EO 3522 University of Michigan - Dual family child support, 1985-1987 (Box R2428)
    - EO 8524 Southern Education Fd. - Public policy & education, 1984-1987 (Box R2428)
    - EO 8525 New York Urban League - Membership campaign, 1985-1987 (Box R2428)
    - EO 8529 Congressional Black Caucus Fd. - Black women econ. Status conf., 1985-1987 (Box R2428)
    - EO 8530 Joint Center for Political Studies-Black scholars conf., 1985-1987 (Box R2428)
    - EO 8531 Voter Education Project - Special com. of the board, 1985-1987 (Box R2428)
    - EO 8533 University of Illinois - Sex composition of occupations, 1985-1989 (Box R2429)
    - EO 8537 Urban Institute - Child care & welfare mothers, 1981-1987 (Box R2429)
    - EO 8538 Institute for Puerto Rican Policy, Inv. - Hispanic voter, 1985-1989 (Box R2429)
    - EO 8541 Cornell University - Econ. dislocation & job loss conf., 1983-1986 (Box R2429)
    - EO 8542 Stack, Carol B., 1985-1989 (Box R2429)
    - EO 8607 National Opinion Res. Center - Youth & labor market, 1985-1986 (Box R2429)
    - EO 8627 Piton Foundation - Denver Concept paper, 1986-1988 (Box R2429)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - HS 8503 Queensland Institute of Med. Res. - Flavirius infections, 1984-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8506 Santoro, Ferrucio, 1982-1987 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8513 University of Victoria - Molecular Studies trypanosomes, 1985-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8516 Mahidol University - Helminth Parasites, 1982-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8523 Johns Hopkins University - Medical ed. & humanities, 1985-1987 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8527 Oxford University - Thalassemia in Pacific Islanders, 1985-1987 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8528 Harvard University - Psychiatry, 1982-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8532 Chen Pei-Yuan, 1985-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8533 Princeton University - Control programs, 1982-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8535 International Epidemiology Assn. - Brazil conf., 1984-1987 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8601 University Hospitals, Cleveland - Onchocera Volvulus, 1984-1988 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8602 Egwang, Thomas, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8603 Freeman, Phyllis K., 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8605 University of Connecticut - Schistosomiasis, 1984-1989 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8606 London School of Hygiene - Leprosy, 1984-1988 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8609 World Fed. for Medical Ed. - Conferences, 1985-1988 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8620 United Nations - World Health Org. - Assembly, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8536 International Federation of Scientific Editors' Associations - Nairobi Symposium, 1985-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8541 Blair Research Laboratory - Praziquantel, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8543 New York University - Malaria Studies In Africa, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8548 Mata, Leonardo 85-87, 19[?] (Box R2431)
    - HS 8549 University of Pennsylvania - Stipend and Health Insurance, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8851 Rosero Bixby, Luis 85-89 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8552 London School Of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Leishmania, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8554 United Nations - World Health Organization - Regional Office for Africa, 1985-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8555 University of California - Parasitic Invasion Symposium (L.A.), 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8556 Johnson, Rollin B., 1983-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8630 Ntambi, James M., 1985-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8632 U.S. & Thai Officials - Consultative Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8644 Emory University - Carter Center - Global Consult. on Health Conference, 1986-1986 (Box R2431)
  - International Relations (IR)
    - IR 8501 French Institute of International Relations - Lebanon Conference, 1984-1987 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8509 Aspen Institute - Governance in a World Economy, 1982-1987 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8512 U.N. Association - U.S. Economic Policy, 1985-1987 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8520 Columbia University - Phadnis, 1985-1986 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8522 Global Interdependence Center - Monetary Conference, 1982-1986 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8523 Southern Africa - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2433)
      One Supplementary Folder - additional folder in [unreadable].
    - IR 8525 International Economics Association - Conference, 1984-198[?] (Box R2433)
    - IR 8526 Western Australian Institute of Technology - Publication, 1985-198[?] (Box R2433)
    - IR 8527 Wilson International Center for Scholars - W. European Program, 1985-1986 (Box R2433)
    - IR 8530 University of Pittsburgh - Atlantic Alliance and Middle East, 1984-1988 (Box R2433)
    - IR 8532 American Assembly - Easing East - West Tensions in the Third World, 1985-1987 (Box R2433)
    - IR 8530 University of Pittsburgh - Atlantic Alliance and Middle East, 1984-1988 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8532 American Assembly - Easing E-W - Tensions in the Third World, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8533 Laba, Roman, 1983-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8534 Center for a New Democracy - Pacific Rim Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8536 Overseas Development Council - World Bank Future, 1985-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8537 World Peace Foundation - Inter - American Collective Security, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8538 Georgetown University - African Debt & Financing Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8541 Potter, William C., 1985-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8601 Journal of Interdisciplinary History - Origins and Prevention of War Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8604 African Association of Political Science - S. African Conference, 1986-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8605 International Human Rights Law Group - Liberian Trials, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8606 Bekich, Darko, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8607 Institute for International Economics - Agriculture and the GATT, 1986-1989 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8608 Emory University - Carter Center - Debt Crisis Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8612 Geneva Graduate Institute of International Studies - Iran-Iraq War Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8615 New York Academy of Sciences - Technology & Risk of War Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8622 Fundación Mediterránea - Economics Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8623 Reiss, Mitchell B., 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8624 Chinese Scholars of International Studies - Conference, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8625 Church of the Pilgrims - Network for Human Rights in Liberia, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8631 Institute for International Economics - Conference, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - PS 8504 International Union for Scientific Study of Population - Italy Conference, 1984-1987 (Box R2435)
    - PS 8507 University of Connecticut - Guinea pig sperm antigen, 1984-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8509 Population Council, Inc. - Immunology Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8510 University of Massachusetts - Progesterone, 1985-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8511 National Academy of Sciences - Population Growth, 1983-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8512 International Women's Health Coalition - Contraceptive Failure Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8513 University of Bahia - Mascarenhas, 1985-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8517 Colegio de México - Latin American Population Program, 1985-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8520 Cornell University - Sperm antibody Formation, 1983-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8521 Leshabari, M.T., 1984-1985 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8526 American Assembly - Population Policy, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8527 Rosero-Bixby, L.A., 1985-1988 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8528 Catholic University (Chile) - Human Reproductive Conference, 1985-1988 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8531 Rockefeller University - Reproduction and Catechol Estrogens, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8532 Rockefeller University - Progestin action in Reproduction, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8601 Institute of Biology - Pituitary and Estrogen Receptors, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8602 Marine Biological Laboratory (Woods Hole) - Video Microscopy Training, 1986-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8611 Aghajanian, A. 86-87 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8613 McMaster University - Indian Scientists Travel, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 8504 University of Nairobi - Women's issues, 1984-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8505 Magubane, Peter, 1984-1988 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8508 Council on Foundations, Inc. - Business leaders Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8511 Obor, Inc. - Solidarity issue, 1983-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8512 National Museums of Kenya - Paleoanthropology school, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8513 International Bank - RF & Indian Agricultural Development, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8514 University of Georgia Law School Association - Rusk Papers, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8516 Williams College - Development Politics and Economics Training Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8517 Andrews, Penelope E., 1984-1988 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8520 Women In Need, Inc. - Child Care, 1985-1988 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8523 New York University - Portfolio Management, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8525 Partnership for Productivity International - African Food Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8529 Indiana University - African Art and Museums Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8530 Women's Funding Coalition - DAWN Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8531 United Nations Office for Emergency Operations in Africa, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8532 Kohler, Robert E., 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8533 National Council for Research on Women - Women's Dialogue (US/USSR), 1984-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8535 Okin, Susan M., 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8537 University of California - Gender & Mobility in America (L.A. ), 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8538 Harvard University - Women's Contribution to Family Economy, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8539 Norton, Mary Beth, 1985-1986 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8540 Cornell University - Children's Thinking About Gender, 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8602 Social Science Research Council - Foreign Language International Studies, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8606 Aga Khan Foundation U.S.A. - Sub-Saharan Africa Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8607 CILECT - Training in Developing Countries, 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8608 Salzburg Seminar - Philanthropy & Non-Profit Institution, 1986-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8609 Gender, Technology & Development - Workshop, 1986-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8611 Independent Sector - Forum & Guidebook on Community Services, 1986-1987 (Box R2438)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - Brambila Paz, Carlos, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - Chillik, Claudio Fabian, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - Rios Nete, Edward Luiz Gonçalves, 1985-1987 (Box R2439)
    - Vilar - Rojas, Cecilia, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A40 Sichuan Medical College - Clinical epidemiology, 1985-198[?] (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A42 Third Annual Meeting of INCLEN, 1984-1986 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A45 Addis Ababa University - Clinical epidemiology, 1985-198[?] (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A47 Shanghai Medical University - Hua Shan Hospital, 1985-19[unreadable] (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A48 Khon Kaen University - Clinical epidemiology - Kiertyia & Sumir, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A49 Chulalongkorn University - Clinical epidemiology - Ayut D., 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A50 West China University of Medical Science - Clinical epidemiology - Lei Bingjun, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A51 Paulista Medical School - Clinical epidemiology - Atallah, Sesso, & Goihman, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A52 Mahidol University - Clinical epidemiology - Nalinee and Nirun, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A55 Fourth Annual Meeting of INCLEN, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85011 - A36 Harvard University - Gossypol, 1982-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A380 Murird, Lion, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A381 Gilbert, Martin, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A382 Bair, Deirdre, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A383 Swearer, Donald K., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A84 Brandt, Allan M., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A385 Gibbard, Allan F., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A386 Kemper, Steven E.G., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A387 Mc Murry, Linda O., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A388 Mack, Phyllis, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A389 Miller, Nancy K., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A390 Offen, Karen, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A391 Thompson, Margaret Susan, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A392 Walkowitz, Judith R., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A393 Kessner, Thomas, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A394 Tick, Judith, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A395 Harris, Michael Wesley, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A396 Johnson, Penelope D., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A397 Herbert, Robert L., 1984-1988 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A398 Keller, Evelyn Fox, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A399 Marcus, Judith, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85014 - A2 Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe - Interdisciplinary artists, 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85018 West Africa Rice Development Association - Staff Support, 1983-1989 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85025 National Humanities Center - Fellowships for Junior Scholars, 1984-1991 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A107 Landry, L. Bartholemew, 1985-1989 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A108 Edwards, Lillie Johnson, 1985-1986 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A109 Thomas, Gail E., 1985-1988 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A110 Perry, Huey L., 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A111 Nelson - Legall, Sharon, 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A112 Paterson - Lewis, Sonja, 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A113 Davis, Thadius M., 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85034 Editorial Projects in Education - Education week, 1984-1985 1987 (Box R2442)
    - RF 85038 Learning in Focus - Films for Television, 1983-1987 (Box R2442)
    - RF 85040 National Arts Stabilization Fund, 1988-1989 (Box R2442)
    - RF 85040 National Arts Stabilization Fund, 1982-1987 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85042 - A3 Yu Yongxin, 1984-1986 1988 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85042 - A4 Mahidol University - Neurosafety primate testing, 1985-1988 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85045 International Planned Parenthood Federation - Developing World Program, 1986-1989 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85045 International Planned Parenthood Federation - Developing World Program, 1984-1985 (Box R2444)
    - RF 85052 Clark College - Public Policy Studies, 1973-1987 (Box R2444)
    - RF 85052 Clark College (Supplementary Folders), 1991 (Box R2445)
    - RF 85052 Clark College - Public Policy Studies (Supplementary folders), 1991 (Box R2446)